Guide to the Harold Jantz collection of early manuscripts, music manuscripts, and autograph albums, 1477-1905 and undated RL.00628
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- List of Bound Manuscripts
  - Swedish (1747): Johan Goransson: Is Atlinga, Stockholm: Lars Salvius, 1747, Printed book (Ms 167)
  - English (1833-1834): Charles G. Bush: Seaman's journal, Manuscript-softbound (Ms 168)
  - German (16th c.-19th c.): A Collection of mostly unbound manuscripts from the 16th through 19th c.: Letters, documents, etc. (Ms 169)
  - English (17th c.): 3 sheets vellum ms. (shelved in Jantz B. Broadside box) (Ms 170)